[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "691848230d734133d0a00370"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f0"
  },
  "question_text": "What is supervised learning?",
  "options": [
    "A type of learning",
    "A type of data",
    "A programming language",
    "None"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "A type of learning",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "691848230d734133d0a00371"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f0"
  },
  "question_text": "Which algorithm is used for classification?",
  "options": [
    "Linear Regression",
    "Decision Tree",
    "K-Means",
    "PCA"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Decision Tree",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "691848230d734133d0a00372"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f0"
  },
  "question_text": "What does ML stand for?",
  "options": [
    "Machine Learning",
    "Model Logic",
    "Mathematical Language",
    "Macro Language"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Machine Learning",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184d690d734133d0a00373"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f5"
  },
  "question_text": "What is a DoS attack?",
  "options": [
    "Denial of Service attack",
    "Data over Security attack",
    "Direct Operating System attack",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Denial of Service attack",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184d690d734133d0a00374"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f5"
  },
  "question_text": "Which protocol is commonly targeted in a SYN flood attack?",
  "options": [
    "TCP",
    "UDP",
    "HTTP",
    "FTP"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "TCP",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184d690d734133d0a00375"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f5"
  },
  "question_text": "What is phishing?",
  "options": [
    "Malicious software",
    "A social engineering attack",
    "Network scanning technique",
    "Firewall misconfiguration"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "A social engineering attack",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184d690d734133d0a00376"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f5"
  },
  "question_text": "Which of these is an example of a network attack?",
  "options": [
    "SQL Injection",
    "Brute Force login",
    "Man-in-the-Middle attack",
    "All of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "All of the above",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184d690d734133d0a00377"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f5"
  },
  "question_text": "What does a firewall do?",
  "options": [
    "Prevents unauthorized access",
    "Monitors system performance",
    "Encrypts data at rest",
    "Manages passwords"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Prevents unauthorized access",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184e51bd9d431b90aefd31"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f2"
  },
  "question_text": "What is a robot?",
  "options": [
    "A machine that can perform tasks automatically",
    "A type of software",
    "A human assistant",
    "None of the above"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "A machine that can perform tasks automatically",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184e51bd9d431b90aefd32"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f2"
  },
  "question_text": "Which type of robot is used for industrial automation?",
  "options": [
    "Humanoid robot",
    "Industrial robot",
    "Service robot",
    "Educational robot"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Industrial robot",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184e51bd9d431b90aefd33"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f2"
  },
  "question_text": "What is the main sensor used in a line-following robot?",
  "options": [
    "Ultrasonic sensor",
    "Infrared sensor",
    "Temperature sensor",
    "Pressure sensor"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Infrared sensor",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69184e51bd9d431b90aefd34"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6915a41094fdff0c11fc28f2"
  },
  "question_text": "Which programming language is commonly used in robotics?",
  "options": [
    "Python",
    "JavaScript",
    "HTML",
    "CSS"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Python",
  "marks": 5
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6918510adc82b90c8a92ce75"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6918510adc82b90c8a92ce74"
  },
  "question_id": "Q001",
  "question_text": "Question 1",
  "options": [
    "a",
    "b",
    "c",
    "d"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "C",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "69185261dc82b90c8a92ce85"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "69185261dc82b90c8a92ce84"
  },
  "question_id": "Q001",
  "question_text": "Question 2",
  "options": [
    "sfvs",
    "dsvsdsdf",
    "sdvvfs",
    "fdvdf"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "C",
  "marks": 1
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c2"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What is a robot?",
  "options": [
    "A machine that performs tasks automatically",
    "A human worker",
    "A software program",
    "A toy"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "A machine that performs tasks automatically",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c3"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which sensor is commonly used for obstacle detection in robots?",
  "options": [
    "Infrared sensor",
    "Temperature sensor",
    "Pressure sensor",
    "Humidity sensor"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Infrared sensor",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c4"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which programming language is widely used in robotics?",
  "options": [
    "Python",
    "HTML",
    "CSS",
    "PHP"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Python",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c5"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What does UAV stand for in robotics?",
  "options": [
    "Unmanned Aerial Vehicle",
    "Universal Automated Vehicle",
    "Unique Artificial Vision",
    "Unidentified Aerial Vehicle"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Unmanned Aerial Vehicle",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c6"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which type of robot mimics human appearance?",
  "options": [
    "Humanoid robot",
    "Industrial robot",
    "Service robot",
    "Autonomous robot"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Humanoid robot",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c7"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which robot is commonly used in factories for assembly?",
  "options": [
    "Industrial robot",
    "Humanoid robot",
    "Medical robot",
    "Exploration robot"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Industrial robot",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c8"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What is the main purpose of a robotic arm?",
  "options": [
    "Manipulate objects",
    "Fly",
    "Scan documents",
    "Play music"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Manipulate objects",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926c9"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which sensor detects distance using sound waves?",
  "options": [
    "Ultrasonic sensor",
    "Infrared sensor",
    "Temperature sensor",
    "Light sensor"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Ultrasonic sensor",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926ca"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What does AI stand for in robotics?",
  "options": [
    "Artificial Intelligence",
    "Automatic Integration",
    "Applied Innovation",
    "Advanced Interface"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Artificial Intelligence",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926cb"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which robot is used for medical surgeries?",
  "options": [
    "Surgical robot",
    "Industrial robot",
    "Humanoid robot",
    "Exploration robot"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Surgical robot",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926cc"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What is the primary function of a mobile robot?",
  "options": [
    "Move autonomously",
    "Manipulate objects",
    "Play music",
    "Print documents"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Move autonomously",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926cd"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which actuator is commonly used in robots for motion?",
  "options": [
    "Servo motor",
    "LED",
    "Switch",
    "Battery"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Servo motor",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926ce"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which type of robot can explore dangerous environments?",
  "options": [
    "Exploration robot",
    "Industrial robot",
    "Humanoid robot",
    "Service robot"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Exploration robot",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926cf"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "Which sensor helps a robot to detect light intensity?",
  "options": [
    "Light sensor",
    "Ultrasonic sensor",
    "Infrared sensor",
    "Temperature sensor"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Light sensor",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6919bf325b6e22f1e9f926d0"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "6919bbc12932be8ff07b70de"
  },
  "question_text": "What is the purpose of a line-following robot?",
  "options": [
    "Follow a pre-defined path",
    "Fly in air",
    "Manipulate objects",
    "Play music"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "Follow a pre-defined path",
  "marks": 2
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "691a2b39b52f9f302ef47ace"
  },
  "quizRef": {
    "$oid": "691a2b39b52f9f302ef47acd"
  },
  "question_id": "Q001",
  "question_text": " xms",
  "options": [
    "mc",
    "m c",
    "c",
    "c"
  ],
  "correctAnswer": "N/A",
  "marks": 2
}]